    var test_name = "Python";
  var questions = [{
    question: "Which of the following is correct about Python?",
    choices: ['It supports functional and structured programming methods as well as OOP', 'It can be used as a scripting language or can be compiled to byte-code for building large applications',
     'It provides very high-level dynamic data types and supports dynamic type checking', 'All of the above'],
    correctAnswer: 2
  },{
    question: "What is the output of print str[2:5] if str = 'Hello World!'?",
    choices: ['llo World!', 'H', 'llo', 'None of the above'],
    correctAnswer: 2
  }, {
    question: "What is the output of print list if tuple = ( 'abcd', 786 , 2.23, 'john', 70.2 )?",
    choices: ['( "abcd", 786 , 2.23, "john", 70.2 )', 'tuple', 'Error', 'None of the above'],
    correctAnswer: 0
  }, {
   question: "Which of the following function convert a String to an object in python?",
    choices: ['repr(x)', 'eval(str)', 'tuple(s)', 'list(s)'],
    correctAnswer: 1
  }, {
    question: "Which of the following operator in python performs exponential (power) calculation on operands?",
    choices: ['**', '//', 'is', 'not in'],
    correctAnswer: 0
  }, {
    question: "Which of the following statement is used when a statement is required syntactically but you do not want any command or code to execute?",
    choices: ['break', 'continue', 'pass', 'None of the above'],
    correctAnswer: 2
  }, {
    question: "Which of the following function checks in a string that all characters are in lowercase?",
    choices: ['islower()', 'isnumeric()', 'isspace()', 'istitle()'],
    correctAnswer: 0
  }, {
    question: "Which of the following function returns the min alphabetical character from the string str?",
    choices: ['lower()', 'lstrip()', 'max(str)', 'min(str)'],
    correctAnswer: 3
  }, {
    question: "What is the output of 3 in [1, 2, 3]?",
    choices: ['true', 'false', 'Error', 'None of the above'],
    correctAnswer: 0
  }, {
    question: "What is the following function reverses objects of list in place?",
    choices: ['list.reverse()', 'list.sort([func])', 'list.pop(obj=list[-1])', 'list.remove(obj)'],
    correctAnswer: 0
  }];

document.write('<script type="text/javascript" src="../js/quiz_javascript.js"></script>');
